indianhomedesign.com 2017-10-28

# Privacy policy

Your privacy is critically important to us. At Cssinfos Technologies LLP ( Indian Home Design Website is owned and operated by Cssinfos Technologies LLP ) we have a few fundamental principles:

  * We don’t ask you for personal information unless we truly need it. (We can’t stand services that ask you for things like your gender or income level for no apparent reason.)
  * We don’t share your personal information with anyone except to comply with the law, develop our products, or protect our rights.
  * We don’t store personal information on our servers unless required for the on-going operation of one of our services.
  * In our Indian Home Design portals, we aim to make it as simple as possible for you to control what’s visible to the public, seen by search engines, kept private, and permanently deleted

**Cssinfos Technologies LLP** (Here in after termed as “ **Cssinfos** ”) operates several websites including [Indian Home Design](http://www.indianhomedesign.com/ "Home Inner") and [Cssinfos.com](http://www.cssinfos.com/ "Cssinfos.com"). It is Cssinfos’s policy to respect your privacy regarding any information we may collect while operating our websites.

**Website Visitors**

Like most website operators, Cssinfos collects non-personally-identifying information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request. Cssinfos’s purpose in collecting non-personally identifying information is to better understand how Cssinfos’s visitors use its website. From time to time, Cssinfos may release non-personally-identifying information in the aggregate, e.g., by publishing a report on trends in the usage of its website.

Cssinfos also collects potentially personally-identifying information like Internet Protocol (IP) addresses for logged in users and for users leaving comments on [Indian Home Design](http://www.indianhomedesign.com/ "Home Inner") portal. Cssinfos only discloses logged in user and commenter IP addresses under the same circumstances that it uses and discloses personally-identifying information as described below, except that Website commenter IP addresses and email addresses are visible and disclosed to the administrators of the [Indian Home Design](http://www.indianhomedesign.com/ "Home Inner") Website where the comment was left.

**Gathering of Personally-Identifying Information**

Certain visitors to Home Inner websites choose to interact with Home Inner website in ways that require Cssinfos to gather personally-identifying information. The amount and type of information that Cssinfos gathers depends on the nature of the interaction. For example, we ask visitors who sign up for a Websites at [Indian Home Design](http://www.indianhomedesign.com/ "Home Inner") to provide a username and email address. Those who engage in transactions with [Indian Home Design](http://www.indianhomedesign.com/ "Home Inner") website – by purchasing access to the Listing, classified, Jobs, Events, Coupons, News, Blogs, CRM service, for example – are asked to provide additional information, including as necessary the personal and financial information required to process those transactions. In each case, Cssinfos collects such information only insofar as is necessary or appropriate to fulfill the purpose of the visitor’s interaction with [Indian Home Design](http://www.indianhomedesign.com/ "Home Inner") website. Cssinfos does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below. And visitors can always refuse to supply personally-identifying information, with the caveat that it may prevent them from engaging in certain website-related activities.

**Aggregated Statistics**

Cssinfos may collect statistics about the behavior of visitors to [Indian Home Design](http://www.indianhomedesign.com/ "Home Inner") website. For instance, Cssinfos may monitor the most popular web pages on the [Indian Home Design](http://www.indianhomedesign.com/ "Home Inner") website or use spam screened by the our / third party service to help identify spam. Cssinfos may display this information publicly or provide it to others. However, Cssinfos does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below.

**Protection of Certain Personally-Identifying Information**

Cssinfos discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only to those of its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations that (i) need to know that information in order to process it on Cssinfos’s behalf or to provide services available at [Indian Home Design](http://www.indianhomedesign.com/ "Home Inner") website, and (ii) that have agreed not to disclose it to others. Some of those employees, contractors and affiliated organizations may be located outside of your home country; by using [Indian Home Design](http://www.indianhomedesign.com/ "Home Inner") website, you consent to the transfer of such information to them. Cssinfos will not rent or sell potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information to anyone. Other than to its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations, as described above, Cssinfos discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only in response to a subpoena, court order or other governmental request, or when Cssinfos believes in good faith that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect the property or rights of Cssinfos, third parties or the public at large. If you are a registered user of an [Indian Home Design](http://www.indianhomedesign.com/ "Home Inner") website and have supplied your email address, [Indian Home Design](http://www.indianhomedesign.com/ "Home Inner") may occasionally send you an email to tell you about new features, solicit your feedback, or just keep you up to date with what’s going on with [Indian Home Design](http://www.indianhomedesign.com/ "Home Inner") website. We primarily use our [Indian Home Design](http://www.indianhomedesign.com/ "Home Inner") Websites to communicate this type of information, so we expect to keep this type of email to a minimum. If you send us a request (for example via a support email or via one of our feedback mechanisms), we reserve the right to publish it in order to help us clarify or respond to your request or to help us support other users. Cssinfos takes all measures reasonably necessary to protect against the unauthorized access, use, alteration or destruction of potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information.

**Cookies**

A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor’s computer, and that the visitor’s browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. [Indian Home Design](http://www.indianhomedesign.com/ "Home Inner") website uses cookies to help us to identify and track visitors, their usage of [Indian Home Design](http://www.indianhomedesign.com/ "Home Inner") website, and their website access preferences. [Indian Home Design](http://www.indianhomedesign.com/ "Home Inner") visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies before using [Indian Home Design](http://www.indianhomedesign.com/ "Home Inner") website, with the drawback that certain features of [Indian Home Design](http://www.indianhomedesign.com/ "Home Inner") website may not function properly without the aid of cookies.

**Business Transfers**

If Cssinfos, or substantially all of its assets, were acquired, or in the unlikely event that Cssinfos goes out of business or enters bankruptcy, user information would be one of the assets that is transferred or acquired by a third party. You acknowledge that such transfers may occur, and that any acquirer of Cssinfos may continue to use your personal information as set forth in this policy.

**Ads**

Ads appearing on any of our websites may be delivered to users by advertising partners, who may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement to compile information about you or others who use your computer. This information allows ad networks to, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This Privacy Policy covers the use of cookies by Cssinfos and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.

Third party vendors, including Google, use cookies to serve ads based on a user’s prior visits to our website.see [how Google uses advertising cookies](https://www.google.com/privacy/ads/#toc-faq).

Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it and its partners to serve ads to our users based on their visit to our sites and/or other sites on the Internet.  
Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [advertising opt-out page.](https://www.google.com/policies/technologies/ads/)

**Comments**

Comments and other content submitted to our service are saved on our servers even they were marked as spam; we store spam comment long enough to use them to improve the service to avoid future spam submission.

**Privacy Policy Changes**

Although most changes are likely to be minor, Cssinfos may change its Privacy Policy from time to time, and in Cssinfos’s sole discretion. Cssinfos encourages visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to its Privacy Policy. If you have a [Indian Home Design](http://www.indianhomedesign.com/ "Home Inner") account, you should also check [Indian Home Design](http://www.indianhomedesign.com/ "Home Inner") Website’s Privacy Policy page for review these changes. Your continued use of this site after any change in this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such change.
